<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="hd3fc6854g8ab2g4191gb6e4g62912342da67" version="1">Forged amidst seething flames, it allows the wearer to channel the mighty essence of ancient dragons. This power empowers them with the ability to command and wield the potent might of dragons, transforming them into a formidable force on the battlefield.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd437e736g47fcg4d9dg8c25gb97bcf62b372" version="1">Ring of Dragonkin</content>
	<content contentuid="h5e0535e6g77e9g4ff7g9774g0858a42a7d7e" version="1">A potent creation of a reclusive sect of blood mages who coveted mastery over the forbidden magic of life force and death's embrace. This ring bestows upon its wearer the ability to manipulate blood and unleash formidable spells upon their foes. However, with forbidden magic, nothing comes without a cost. Wield it wisely.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8b612f98g5c59g4fcagb781gc8ea7f724dee" version="1">Ring of Blood Oath</content>
	<content contentuid="hc7cf8a27gcea7g43bfgba89g139fc4598a1e" version="1">A relic of the night. Shrouds its wearer in veils of darkness, granting the gift of silent movement and the power to catch foes off guard, making it the ideal tool for those who thrive in the shadows.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a5cc273g794bg4431gb235g5c691c8ca63d" version="1">Ring of Ethereal Phantoms</content>
	<content contentuid="h3e442d1cg9096g4304gb645g714557994b19" version="1">A revered relic hailing from a long-forgotten era when peace reigned between the realms of light and dark, it was crafted by ancient beings who sought to harmonize these contrasting forces. Allows its wearer to harness both radiant and shadowy energies, enabling them to heal and smite in equal measure.</content>
	<content contentuid="he6645c7fgbcbdg4582gb26ag8bbce3c3201f" version="1">Ring of Dusk and Dawn</content>
	<content contentuid="h72ed288fg81b7g45dfgab5egfd33d2d95b74" version="1">Forged by a sly mastermind, this ring embodies the essence of a cunning joker. It allows its wearer to twist fate in their favor, enabling the use of clever tricks and tactics.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5ce20789ga993g4a23g8897gd966f7d3b9b1" version="1">Sly Joker's Ring</content>
	<content contentuid="hf68a8138g2d29g4bc4g8ca3g6bb69fc17d33" version="1">A sinister artifact once adorned by a Mind Flayer. Granting its wearer access to telepathic abilities and immense psychic power.</content>
	<content contentuid="h07926688gf643g47a3g9106g8f6c8b05410f" version="1">The Mind Ring</content>
	<content contentuid="h2923021fg59cag4429g8b3bgdfa9a72093ff" version="1">Crafted deep within the heart of the Githyanki's astral enclaves. Grants its wearer the ability to command the very essence of the battlefield. This ancient relic carries the weight of countless battles, where Githyanki champions have harnessed its power to transcend the ordinary.</content>
	<content contentuid="h45a37424gadb0g4362g8a14g1551dc77ef79" version="1">Astral Legacy Ring</content>
	<content contentuid="h5579fdbeg7592g4f67gbedbgebafb867475c" version="1">A vile artifact. Thrives on the whispers of the dead, granting its bearer the dread powers of vampirism, including life-draining abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="hafdb08d3gc546g4b26gbebbg18fbabbe3483" version="1">Ring of Veilwalker's Hunger</content>
	<content contentuid="h49e61245gdb32g4c1eg9a54g20fc3599a179" version="1">This meticulously crafted ring resonates with the thunderous might of the gods, bearing the divine blessings of the gods. When worn, it grants enhanced lightning affinity, allowing the wearer to invoke the thunderous power and unleash the tempest's wrath upon their foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6a43a8b7g3faeg47d4g8cf7gfdc61b32e5dd" version="1">Thunder God's Ring</content>
	<content contentuid="h8eec4aacg32acg4098gaae3g4223b17a66ab" version="1">Crafted amid the desolate tundras of Icewind Dale. Carries the essence of its frigid birthplace, allowing its wearer wield the relentless power of winter's fury.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd0288849gb096g4125gbae6g00d7894bf0e0" version="1">Ring of Cryomancer's Wrath</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1bded44g94feg4535g9340gfae2a7f03528" version="1">Once wielded by a prominent leader among the "Absolute" cult. Forged through forbidden and blood-soaked rituals, it grants its possessor mastery over necrotic energies, becoming an accursed symbol of the leader's malevolent reign, casting a shadow of despair upon all who cross their path.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a8ffd32g4c88g4ce2gb21agcdea40c70981" version="1">Darkmaster's Legacy Ring</content>
	<content contentuid="h6a75d60bg3aacg41abgb43bgc4b8c92a0b3a" version="1">An exquisitely crafted ring which serves as a testament to the power of the mind. Enhance the wearer's mental and mystical prowess, a true symbol of mastery over unseen forces and a potent tool for combat.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd952e337gf39dg49feg9b8cgc635b1b4a263" version="1">Ring of Mental Acuity</content>
	<content contentuid="h46129d9cgf0fbg4601gad13g75043ecd7b9f" version="1">An artifact of infernal supremacy, once wielded by the unyielding Lord of Flames, it grants mastery over hellish flames and commands the incendiary fury of the abyss. With this infernal might, you summon a dread ally, ready to serve and unleash devastating power upon the battlefield.</content>
	<content contentuid="hde98e3f1gad51g4575gbcb2g42bf97a44c90" version="1">Ring of Blazing Hellfire</content>
	<content contentuid="h8ad42120g5b1fg40a7gbdebg21d4d4b8bfcf" version="1">A primal relic of sheer force. Bolsters its possessor's physical prowess, imbuing them with the raw might and resilience reminiscent of a formidable hill giant.</content>
	<content contentuid="h89297193gbdcdg4fbbga5f0g745358e3f85d" version="1">Talisman of Hill Giant Strength</content>
	<content contentuid="hb9b7132ag3233g4d8bga1ecg95b7d83eac23" version="1">A treasured relic, was created by an ancient circle of revered healers. It radiates with profound healing capabilities, serving as a symbol of hope and restoration. It embodies the unwavering dedication of those who seek to mend the wounds of the world across the ages.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9d64866ega009g4495ga585ga6e2fa024065" version="1">The Lifebringer's Amulet</content>
	<content contentuid="h5f724a33gd083g4863g82ebg7940b6c64f19" version="1">A talisman of blazing power, was worn by a powerful Firewalker as a symbol of mastery over the flames, it serves as a testament to the control and discipline of its bearer. Grants the ability to wield the flames with precision and finesse.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1184c4fdg5a4dg4d55gb2dbg6715a1b42f50" version="1">Firewalker's Talisman</content>
	<content contentuid="h5907aaadg2416g4699gbbdfg67cf7fe54616" version="1">A mysterious and potent relic of unknown origin, this enigmatic talisman confers upon its possessor a diverse range of mystical abilities, serving as a bridge between the veiled domains of nature and the enigmatic arcane realms.</content>
	<content contentuid="h68c23fafgccb5g43fagba3bg7660fb25b326" version="1">Talisman of Mystical Versatility</content>
	<content contentuid="h62a2c1c9ge7a2g4aaag9f6fg568ed82133c6" version="1">Forged in reverence to the legendary ranger Drizzt Do'Urden, this amulet bestows formidable prowess upon its wearer, allowing them to summon loyal companions and attain mastery over Drizzt's renowned arsenal. It stands as a testament to Drizzt's indomitable legacy, infusing its possessor with the unwavering spirit of a true ranger.</content>
	<content contentuid="h039e2e7cg8b06g40ebgb425gb1c1f75f4c6d" version="1">Drizzt's Shadowclaw Amulet</content>
	<content contentuid="hdd55a8f3gcb24g43c3g82dfg462233c54778" version="1">Once worn by a legendary hero, a mighty guardian of nature. Grants its wearer the ability to shift forms and harness the very essence of nature's power. A symbol of the deep bond between its wearer and nature's untamed forces.</content>
	<content contentuid="he34f7e0dgfd6dg42b4gac40g21b94b7e423a" version="1">Amulet of the Shapeshifter</content>
	<content contentuid="h6adc1f47g1090g427agb59bgc7b26a46f1ae" version="1">Forged in the heart of the Absolute's inner sanctum, this sinister amulet carries with it a legacy steeped in darkness. It is a somber relic that attests to the unwavering loyalty of a true soul who dedicated themselves to the Absolute's cause, channeling the cult's relentless might through this malevolent artifact. "Praise The Absolute!"</content>
	<content contentuid="h94c700a0gd2f6g4c5bgb6b0g17f1507971eb" version="1">Zealot's Talisman of Devotion</content>
	<content contentuid="h1e90784bg5831g4737ga31dg019e17410eb2" version="1">A revered relic passed down through generations of witchers. Forged with ancient craftsmanship and enchanted with the ability to detect monsters and magic, it signifies the wearer's commitment to hunting down the supernatural and the unknown.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc8aa6f3eg874eg4f6fg95c9gc3fba3a1c83e" version="1">The Witcher's Medallion</content>
	<content contentuid="ha773ddf7g0cd9g480bg97a8gc772f8f72dba" version="1">Within the depths of this hidden trove, an array of enchanting rings and amulets awaits discovery. Each possesses the potential to bestow upon its wearer unparalleled mystical prowess. These relics, steeped in the magic of Eldertide Armament, hold the key to unlocking untold power and secrets, offering a tantalizing allure to those who dare to seek their might.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd0dc2b77ga6afg4240g826ag9196972b2500" version="1">Mystic Eldertide Cache</content>
	<content contentuid="h93f029f0g7952g4b09gb1cbga66f016f1007" version="1">Once the prized possession of the enigmatic Tasha, exudes an aura of arcane authority. Those who wear the amulet may find themselves blessed with enhanced magical prowess, but with such empowerment comes the ever-present whisper of Tasha's influence, a subtle reminder of the witch queen's enduring presence in the artifact.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef9da7d1g80f7g4900g9103gb57e924afc29" version="1">Witch Queen Amulet</content>
	<content contentuid="h7ab43710g3d35g4f94ga5afg59c322750a63" version="1">Cauldron of Arcane Whispers</content>
	<content contentuid="h5accac72gb8bcg4785gb3b5gbd17204d23b5" version="1">Tasha's Compendium of Alchemical Arts</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a0d1bf2gac25g4909g826cgd47fc86bb15b" version="2">Magical book filled with Tasha's curated elixirs and potions. Unlock the secrets of mystical concoctions, from healing remedies to potent enhancements. A must-have for alchemists seeking the touch of the enigmatic witch herself.</content>
	<content contentuid="h77b4fd63g781bg4d8bgb270g204c27a13826" version="2">Dear Alchemists and Seekers of Magic,&lt;br&gt;Within these pages, I share the alchemical secrets that have danced in the cauldron of my creation. &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Tasha's Compendium of Alchemical Arts&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; unveils a gallery of elixirs, each a manifestation of my arcane endeavors. May these recipes ignite your own magical pursuits and awaken the alchemist within.&lt;br&gt;Brew with wonder, Tasha.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Eldertide: Blast - Divine Bone Shard&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Eldertide: Rupture - Black Oleander&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Eldertide: Eruption - Chasm Creeper&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Charismatic Brilliance - Planetar Feather&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Unleashed Chaos - Nothic Eye&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Obscure Necrosis - Night Orchid&lt;br&gt;Potion of Terrain Traversal - Acorn Truffle&lt;br&gt;Quicksilver Strike Elixir - Mergrass&lt;br&gt;Potion of Critical Favor - Unicorn Horn&lt;br&gt;Potion of Prismatic Deflection - Imp Patagium&lt;br&gt;Potion of Balefire - Yellow Musk Creeper Petals&lt;br&gt;Lifewarden Elixir - Pegasus Feather&lt;br&gt;Elixir of Dawnshade - Shadowroot Sac&lt;br&gt;Elixir of the Gods - Belladonna&lt;br&gt;Potion of the Thunder Giant - Cloud Giant Finger&lt;br&gt;Potion of the Archmagi - Dragon Egg Mushroom</content>
	<content contentuid="h8794182cgeff6g4feagac77g9d16947641b5" version="1">The Chronicles of Eldertide</content>
	<content contentuid="hbcb7c8edg8f14g442agb058g823a0ff690d8" version="2">Within the hallowed pages of this mystical tome, protected by the realm's most formidable and loyal heroes, lies a repository of arcane secrets. Unravel its knowledge to discover the hidden lore of powerful artifacts, and seize the opportunity to embark on a journey in search of higher power.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4bbdafa4g3641g475aga67egbf795609638d" version="2">In the ancient days of the Forgotten Realms, a collection of mystical artifacts emerged, known as the &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. Each item held a fragment of ancient arcane might, possessing unparalleled magical prowess. However, as the ages unfolded, the artifacts were scattered across the realms, hidden to safeguard their incredible power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whispers of the &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; spread through the ages, captivating the hearts of adventurers and scholars alike. Tales of untold abilities, unparalleled strengths, and the promise of unimaginable magic fueled the desire to reunite the scattered artifacts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legends spoke of a mystical ring, said to channel the very power of the thunder god. A ring steeped in the essence of Avernus, beckoned to those seeking both power and peril. Alongside them, an enigmatic amulet, adorned with the symbols of flickering flames, It was said that the amulet allowed the wearer to harness the essence of fire, becoming a firewalker. Yet, the locations of these artifacts remained obscured, lost in the annals of time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the seeker of lost knowledge, your destiny intertwines with the &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. The weave of magic calls out to you, urging you to embark on a perilous journey. Unravel the mysteries of the past, navigate the forgotten realms, and heed the whispers of power that echo through the ages. The &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; await, scattered yet united in their call to a chosen soul—will you be the one to answer?</content>
	<content contentuid="hbc782b06g11d4g4e9bg9053g2f2f21c90527" version="1">Thaddeus Shadowthorn, Journal Entry #1</content>
	<content contentuid="h5ddaa7e2g777ag4febgadbfg77bdcce6ebb3" version="1">Weathered pages from the journal of Thaddeus Shadowthorn, a Warlock bound by the Pact of the Great Old One, seeking the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="he3b7c869g4891g40a0gb199g7286a6060c76" version="2">As ink gracefully meets parchment, I embark on a perilous journey into the heart of the Forgotten Realms, in search of the elusive &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;. Whispers of their power have beckoned to my arcane senses, and the time has come to unravel the mysteries hidden across this legendary realm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cryptic map, obtained from a mysterious figure in a dimly lit Waterdeep tavern, serves as my guide.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4954448cgf01bg40aeg81fbg90fb13a80525" version="1">Thaddeus Shadowthorn, Journal Entry #2</content>
	<content contentuid="h18e251a4g14f9g4ac0gb9b9g8a777a993ac1" version="1">Weathered pages from the journal of Thaddeus Shadowthorn, a Warlock bound by the Pact of the Great Old One, seeking the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb295b468gb0a9g48b1g8452g437ca8170c17" version="2">Navigating through challenges in the Sword Coast's forests and the Anauroch Desert, I stumbled upon a revelation in Myth Drannor that hints at one of the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; sacred relics - &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Ring of Ethereal Phantoms&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amidst the pursuit, a Deathbringer, an elite warrior of Bhaal, appeared. The struggle intensified as we clashed. In the shadowy ruins, a fierce battle unfolded, culminating in a powerful Eldritch Blast as I drew power from my patron, crumbling my enemy to dust. The echoes mark a decisive moment in my quest for &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;, where danger, enlightenment, and a certainty that this wasn't my final battle in the search for those forgotten relics.</content>
	<content contentuid="hab5b29a5ge500g47b1ga73cg356b4262aabb" version="1">Thaddeus Shadowthorn, Journal Entry #3</content>
	<content contentuid="hf210cfd5g5574g45c6g9fe9g7b016fb5ae23" version="1">Weathered pages from the journal of Thaddeus Shadowthorn, a Warlock bound by the Pact of the Great Old One, seeking the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0f54d906g9eebg4d01gb4fcg176481bca7b0" version="2">In the heart of Myth Drannor, my search reached a dead end. Despite being filled with encounters and discoveries, my journey concluded with a heavy heart.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; remain elusive, slipping through my grasp like ethereal wisps in the bustling city of Waterdeep. The rumors, once promising, now echo with the hollow resonance of disappointment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Were these artifacts ever more than mere whispers and fantasies within the realms of Faerûn? The journal bears witness to my quest's end, leaving me to reflect upon the nature of my pursuit and the elusive history of these artifacts.</content>
	<content contentuid="haa144b07ga533g4764g9e76gbe9c08c6c72e" version="1">Sir Darian Ironheart, journal entry #1</content>
	<content contentuid="hffdc8c02gb7c7g49cegbaf3g44ed444a2b7b" version="1">Frayed entries disclose the journey of Sir Darian Ironheart, a Paladin sworn to the Oath of Vengeance in his righteous pursuit for the Eldertide.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd5b1062agac0bg4ee3g9c56g8ab3ab481faf" version="2">With unwavering faith in the divine, I embark on a sacred quest to seek the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; within the vast lands of the Forgotten Realms. Clad in armor, sword at my side, the journey commences. A celestial guide whispered of an ancient prophecy, foretelling the convergence of destinies and the revelation of powerful artifacts amidst the diverse landscapes of Faerûn. The divine light guides my steps as I set forth on this holy pilgrimage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h11da171cg8fd6g43ffg9060g313eedd570ed" version="1">Sir Darian Ironheart, journal entry #2</content>
	<content contentuid="h7cf7fa59g4f56g4874gb015g497564676362" version="1">Frayed entries disclose the journey of Sir Darian Ironheart, a Paladin sworn to the Oath of Vengeance in his righteous pursuit for the Eldertide.</content>
	<content contentuid="h561c6859g677eg45b1g895dg2d941096bda9" version="2">Amid ancient carvings, a celestial sigil reveals a potential &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; relic deep within the Underdark's labyrinthine depths.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the heart of the Underdark, I face a beholder, dodging its destructive magic with unwavering faith. With celestial powers by my side, I exploit a hidden vulnerability, defeating the beholder. Now, standing victorious, I press forward toward the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; concealed in the subterranean abyss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet, the divine whispers remain cryptic, answers eluding me. Each step forward tests my resolve, but I maintain my faith.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4cc23e28g01deg4e5dg809fg198bc22840d5" version="1">Sir Darian Ironheart, journal entry #3</content>
	<content contentuid="h2b054cacge204g46abg95ffg314c8cf35f73" version="1">Frayed entries disclose the journey of Sir Darian Ironheart, a Paladin sworn to the Oath of Vengeance in his righteous pursuit for the Eldertide.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0b880388g6d6eg4d46g8c20g1b32ca6a1e69" version="2">Despite my devout quest, the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt; remain hidden within the sacred tapestry of the divine plan amidst the vast realms of Faerûn. Disappointment settles like a heavy cloud upon my soul. I close this chapter of my journey with reflection, pondering the will of the divine and the mysteries that elude even the most steadfast champions.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1241b4adgdd21g41edgbabdg611caed69c73" version="1">Lyra Emberflame, journal entry #1</content>
	<content contentuid="hf0e818c0g2738g4236gbff0gf8a417ac78f6" version="1">Worn manuscripts divulge the odyssey of Lyra Emberflame, a sorceress bearing the Draconic Bloodline, in search of the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="h430a2485gd6cfg4a66g92fagb57c45cc6a91" version="2">In the arcane glow of my study in the city of Silverymoon, I embark on a journey to unravel the mysteries of the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;. My sorcerous instincts, drawn to the mystical, lead me through the bustling streets of Baldur's Gate, following the cryptic threads of rumor and legend. A tattered grimoire acquired from a curious merchant in Waterdeep contains whispers of untold power, beckoning me to explore unseen realms and unveil hidden secrets.</content>
	<content contentuid="h436ec8fbgf400g4c43g8b31g3b8ba260e699" version="1">Lyra Emberflame, journal entry #2</content>
	<content contentuid="h7bb50b21gfc82g4a28gadc0gb9f1a56ad0d6" version="1">Worn manuscripts divulge the odyssey of Lyra Emberflame, a sorceress bearing the Draconic Bloodline, in search of the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha47df321gebbeg4fc7gb070g7d921ab2dfcb" version="2">Guided by arcane whispers, my journey winds through perilous terrains and ancient libraries, navigating from the lore-laden archives of Candlekeep to the menacing towers of Thay. Within the Library of the Lady in Selûne's Light, a revelation surfaces - a forgotten manuscript hints at the possible location of the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firewalker's Talisman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, one of the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;, concealed beneath the ruins of an ancient underground fire temple located in the high mountains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My adventure takes me through towering peaks and treacherous landscapes, each step echoing with the whispering winds. The journey takes a more perilous turn as I venture into the smoldering territory guarded by a fierce red dragon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trail to the ancient fire temple leads me to the heart of a red dragon's lair. With the looming presence of the majestic creature, I patiently await the opportune moment, slipping through shadows to avoid direct confrontation. Deep within the lair, amidst echoing roars and the glow of molten gold, I discover a fiery ember. Its radiant warmth signals my proximity to the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firewalker's Talisman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h12b37ef7g8e34g4f35g9920g0c7bc1b8d090" version="1">Lyra Emberflame, journal entry #3</content>
	<content contentuid="hb83b48abg792eg4a8eg8459gc2e18fd8b73b" version="1">Worn manuscripts divulge the odyssey of Lyra Emberflame, a sorceress bearing the Draconic Bloodline, in search of the Eldertide Armaments.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc86d015fg15e1g42c7g9049g969b9d754fd1" version="2">The pinnacle of my arcane odyssey is marked by a bittersweet moment. I finally lay hands on the coveted &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firewalker's Talisman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, one of the &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;. The thrill of accomplishment courses through me as the ancient artifact graces my grasp, promising untold power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet, my triumph is short-lived. The red dragon, concealed in the shadows, springs forth with a surprise attack. In a brave but desperate struggle, I face the ferocity of the dragon's onslaught. Amidst the fiery chaos of our encounter, the Talisman slips from my fingers, plummeting into the abyss, lost once again to the annals of time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dragon's assault intensifies, and in a daring escape, I narrowly evade its wrath. The &lt;i&gt;Eldertide Armaments&lt;/i&gt;, once within my possession, now lies obscured in the unknown depths. I emerge battered but alive, one of the fortunate few to have held the elusive relic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I recount the tale, the taste of disappointment mingles with the pride of holding the &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firewalker's Talisman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, a fleeting encounter with the arcane wonders that elude the grasp of even the most intrepid seekers.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf8a84875g3b0ag4280gb7c9g5c52f406e306" version="1">Quicksilver Strike Elixir</content>
	<content contentuid="ha3850e7cg39bcg4e8aga41ag3ba99cad7442" version="2">As you hold the vial, a shimmering liquid swirls within, embodying the swiftness of quicksilver. It seems to anticipate your movements, promising precision in strikes and agility.</content>
	<content contentuid="h996a30bbg2dd5g4a3bgbd06gafc8d53b3b1d" version="1">When consumed, gain a +2 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and Dexterity Saving Throws, alongside an increase in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h467ce645gfd65g4f38g9f26gb9ecba67d71c" version="1">Quicksilver</content>
	<content contentuid="h03a26b96ge55fg4e9bg8eaag00f7d695b39c" version="1">The affected entity moves with unparalleled grace, gaining a +2 bonus to both &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and Dexterity Saving Throws, character &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; is increased.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5f12cb05g4eccg4885gacb6g4194320373f9" version="1">Potion of Critical Favour</content>
	<content contentuid="heb106909gc48bg4de2g8644g29ebed6c9645" version="2">A vial shimmering with an uncanny precision, almost predicting your every move.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7e93b851gd978g4631gb648geb1bb5e3564c" version="1">After consumption, you gain a 1d4 bonus to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, reducing the number needed to score a critical hit by 1.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfdbf4e28gb11dg41ffg92f6g431efc624aab" version="1">Critical Favour</content>
	<content contentuid="h78083e2fg0ee8g440eg8dd4gbf798c6cfeeb" version="1">Affected entity experience heightened agility, gaining 1d4 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and the threshold for landing a critical hit is lowered by 1.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c3bed0ag2d42g4631gbe55g8d7eaccb21d5" version="1">Potion of Prismatic Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="heb26951age7e0g4b9fg851bg92802383afa6" version="2">A myriad of hues suspended, as if it harbors the very spectrum itself.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0de27882g9ee6g492cgbc61g2e4b049cefd0" version="1">When consumed, a portion of incoming damage directed at you are refracted and deflected back toward the attacker. Increasing your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; by 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces the effects of other Eldertide elixirs upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="h86e147edg2c21g4dc7g8fa6g999f51357966" version="1">Prismatic Barrier</content>
	<content contentuid="h791ba7b1ge2b8g48e6gbaa2g256aea78a1fd" version="1">The affected entity gains the ability to partially reflect incoming damage, returning 1d6 damage back at the attacker. Increases your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; by 2</content>
	<content contentuid="h5cefb53ag395bg432fg81d2g7e03a5a33cc0" version="1">Radiant Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="hcc0ba500g9ca8g495agaf0cg4096ff798e56" version="1">Deflect radiant damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0b67a638g27eeg45f5ga673gc2b2daf925d0" version="1">Lightning Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="h9b6d8669g7793g4987g8fb6g99273d23243e" version="1">Deflect lightning damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd0fbbb65g0a8bg4ca5g86c5g4643bba237a3" version="1">Necrotic Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="h69360588gec54g4bb6g8bb3gf05bbd0f9316" version="1">Deflect necrotic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h46a81c27g50e0g4639gab11g2a4653e512a2" version="1">Cold Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="hc353480agdb77g482bgbfbdg6526f29fb579" version="1">Deflect cold damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a2256d3gb19eg4145gbe2agc4edb76bb48c" version="1">Fire Deflection</content>
	<content contentuid="h3a429e4bg1d85g4725gb53fg01f177a1747b" version="1">Deflect fire damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h85c44ffdgf948g4de1gaa24g9dfe782835cc" version="1">Potion of Balefire</content>
	<content contentuid="haf7ea4afgc6adg4844g8983g19d59dd9cba0" version="2">A spectral inferno waiting to be unleashed.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfed6ba0ega582g4c79g88a9g4b76dde02e90" version="1">After consumption, your main melee weapon ignites with ethereal fire, dealing extra fire damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a0eeeb0gdbdcg4865g8b5ag0b46b93fe195" version="1">Balefire</content>
	<content contentuid="h6f6b7e4dg0989g4e6eg919dg398495061a84" version="1">The affected entity's main melee weapon becomes imbued with spectral flames, dealing extra [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h90c1d907gb402g4ceagbcf6g69d4feecb4a5" version="1">Arms of Balefire</content>
	<content contentuid="ha0b66a06ga55eg4ceeg9020g36a728f598e1" version="1">This weapon deals additional fire damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha6fa33c8gd462g4b27g9fdbgf33d086e2b93" version="1">Lifewarden Elixir</content>
	<content contentuid="h0beb4d7egeb13g4c46gb8e2g5e5cb3d656fb" version="2">As you gaze upon this swirling elixir, it seems to pulse with vitality, promising restoration and resilience.</content>
	<content contentuid="h648fef0bgd650g4f45gae8bg55d636c3b753" version="1">Recover [1] and stops &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BURNING"&gt;Burning&lt;/LSTag&gt;, regenerate [2] at turn start, you gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Constitution Saving Throws.</content>
	<content contentuid="h77bb2e4bgae17g48e1gb91cgdddd500c5462" version="1">Healing Factor</content>
	<content contentuid="h00b7a350gb84cg45d9g8393gb8a509c2d3ca" version="1">Affected entity regain [1] at the start of turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdfcccb17gf3f3g4460g9ba7g55630d50b543" version="1">Elixir of Dawnshade</content>
	<content contentuid="hde8dcdb9gabf3g4be0gb1a1gf56175b00f18" version="2">Swirling with ethereal hues, this elixir captivates with the delicate balance between light and shadow.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfd9c20e1gab45g4957g927eg6c5155d34eb0" version="1">Grants immunity to fear, and gains &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to both radiant and necrotic damage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces the effects of other Eldertide elixirs upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb384da3cg7db8g43e7ga49egb4b35afd0cf9" version="1">Ethereal Resilience</content>
	<content contentuid="hf2ecc743gdd92g4f14g9d57gb34612b5b473" version="1">The affected entity can't be &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt; and has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to both radiant and necrotic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc67bbbfbg5ff7g40f9ga954g9f44bb0f4e45" version="1">Elixir of the Gods</content>
	<content contentuid="hf22fd40dgca0dg4b7bg89f2g0c9485d54e67" version="2">A manifestation of divine power coursing through your mortal form.</content>
	<content contentuid="habe5aeccg9602g4062g9cdcgad0885bcffea" version="1">Raise all of your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityScore"&gt;Ability Scores&lt;/LSTag&gt; to a minimum of 20.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces the effects of other Eldertide elixirs upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="he29ebe10g9b47g464eg83b3gc2ace50d31a0" version="2">Unto a God</content>
	<content contentuid="h9d1b07b3gd80dg4993g9654gbc6fa6d50382" version="2">Raise all of your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityScore"&gt;Ability Scores&lt;/LSTag&gt; to minimum [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hf408c4abg97c2g45c8gb01cg8663af656637" version="1">Elixir of the Thunder Giant</content>
	<content contentuid="h3e7932e9g0a95g4820gbc21gd2258b26499b" version="2">As you hold this potion, the air around it crackles with electrifying energy, a miniature storm encapsulated in a glass vessel.</content>
	<content contentuid="h35f080fbg32edg43d6g9b5dgcd54e67d82d7" version="1">Grow in size, granting temporary hit points and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to physical damage. Attacks you make unleash a thunderous explosion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces the effects of other Eldertide elixirs upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b8bc7c6g9e68g45degbf6bged9960f93a93" version="2">Aspect of Thunder Giant</content>
	<content contentuid="h118ee3c0gcb54g4a12gac45g9b8c8fdf8356" version="2">The affected entity is Enlarged and gains temporary hit points equal to one-fourth of its maximum hit points, along with &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Physical damage. Attacks you make deals additional [1] in a [2] radius.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc055cdedg5423g4c3dg8e42gf9f5d1dd9803" version="1">Potion of the Archmagi</content>
	<content contentuid="hc57d8066g1bb5g4c3eg9e5ag19788a3b1973" version="2">Glimmering with arcane potential, this potion whispers secrets of the highest magic.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf1b371dfg4ef3g4a74ga18cga47af1d17c5b" version="1">Replenishes up to level 3 spell slots. Gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and Saving Throws against spells and magical effects. </content>
	<content contentuid="h34560c5eg86f2g4956g99f3gabfcef476b0a" version="2">Archmage Embodiment</content>
	<content contentuid="h54eea3aega31dg4428ga65agd532b824a72a" version="2">You've restored up to level 3 spell slots, have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and on Saving Throws against spells and magical effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6946d85cg2303g4b05g85ddgc19a50ba6de0" version="2">&lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; of the Archmage</content>
	<content contentuid="h025182a9g2a81g4d36g945bga4edee5a61e2" version="2">Has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Saving Throws against spells and magical effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdc741ebaga974g4953gac40gaf84acd12905" version="1">Elixir of Eldertide: Blast</content>
	<content contentuid="h1c4aa436ge491g47c4g9d2fgeb1725a5c821" version="2">This potent and magical elixir crackles with an ethereal light, whispering ancient Eldertide incantations.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0b6474d4g758fg468fgb5dcgedc89f8dfd59" version="1">Modifies Eldertide Armaments projectile spells, forcefully pushing affected targets up to [1] away from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces effects of other 'Elixirs of Eldertide' upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="h95630fdfgace7g4520ga434g03f085b38d04" version="1">Eldertide Attunement: Blast</content>
	<content contentuid="ha4d1e5e9gea59g4be0g84f7g2f31bdfc390e" version="1">Grants Eldertide projectile spells the ability to push affected targets [1] away from you.</content>
	<content contentuid="he1e6003egb733g4468gb805g8a7efdc33641" version="2">Eldertide Attunement: Blast</content>
	<content contentuid="hbac99a9fg3cf6g4c4fg941dgb61491dfb721" version="3">When you hit a creature with Eldertide spells, you can push the creature up to [1] away from you.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf05ef0cegdf7cg4c43g8c6fg322ae793dbe6" version="5">The effect applies to the following Eldertide spells: &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_FingerOfDeath"&gt;Finger of Death&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_CataclysmBlast"&gt;Cataclysm Blast&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_JudgmentBolt"&gt;Judgment Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_ShadowsRetribution"&gt;Shadows Retribution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_Annihilation"&gt;Annihilation&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_RayOfTheInfernalPhoenix"&gt;Ray of the Infernal Phoenix&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_BewitchingBolt"&gt;Bewitching Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h205d9080g78f0g41b3g9857g7c68771a0aca" version="1">Elixir of Eldertide: Rupture</content>
	<content contentuid="h03a30f62ga982g4828g8bc5g196be33d55ec" version="2">Within this mystical elixir resides the essence of primordial Eldertide magic, a tempest that rends the fabric of reality, leaving echoes of rupture in its wake.</content>
	<content contentuid="he07afe2bgae60g4567g82f8g0b32707d487a" version="1">Modifies Eldertide Armaments projectile spells, causing affected targets to suffer an additional [1] upon impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces effects of other 'Elixirs of Eldertide' upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6a26c045g1e48g46f7gbdf7gb8f555db763c" version="1">Eldertide Attunement: Rupture</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a0ff09cg8d0ag4bbagafceg9515433ea16a" version="1">Grants Eldertide projectile spells the ability to deal an extra [1] upon impact.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfc72df1dgbcffg453ag9beag275ca9bfc461" version="2">Eldertide Attunement: Rupture</content>
	<content contentuid="h6c3ad177g57e0g4bb4gbf5fg149d67053147" version="3">When you hit a creature with Eldertide spells, you deal extra [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h5d2d2d58gbf7ag41e9gbd5eg24bb060a707b" version="5">The effect applies to the following Eldertide spells: &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_FingerOfDeath"&gt;Finger of Death&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_CataclysmBlast"&gt;Cataclysm Blast&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_JudgmentBolt"&gt;Judgment Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_ShadowsRetribution"&gt;Shadows Retribution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_Annihilation"&gt;Annihilation&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_RayOfTheInfernalPhoenix"&gt;Ray of the Infernal Phoenix&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_BewitchingBolt"&gt;Bewitching Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4bd48f31g7284g40aeg897fgfb498106e33f" version="1">Elixir of Eldertide: Eruption</content>
	<content contentuid="h3bff9f48g7678g4c37g8d03g7551f59d14d1" version="2">A potent and condensed force of Eldertide lies dormant within this elixir, ready to unleash havoc upon impact.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1fcc2206g403ag452ag87ceg9af6c36885f6" version="1">Modifies Eldertide Armaments projectile spells, triggering an explosion that deals [1] in a [2] radius upon impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces effects of other 'Elixirs of Eldertide' upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdbcf6fcegbdafg4aeeg9070gcea61a1969b7" version="1">Eldertide Attunement: Eruption</content>
	<content contentuid="h16119a2cgc98eg402ag8a0fg4a0f8e557859" version="1">Grants Eldertide projectile spells the ability to trigger an explosion that deals [1] in a [2] radius.</content>
	<content contentuid="he1ba06d4g048fg4903gbb0cge44a405ba53d" version="2">Eldertide Attunement: Eruption</content>
	<content contentuid="hac17a517g7203g44fcg9de8g4e2dfccc7602" version="3">When you hit a creature with Eldertide spells, it triggers an explosion that deals [1] in a [2] radius.</content>
	<content contentuid="h15308df6gcb43g4bfeg906fgbec968aa07eb" version="5">The effect applies to the following Eldertide spells: &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_FingerOfDeath"&gt;Finger of Death&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_CataclysmBlast"&gt;Cataclysm Blast&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_JudgmentBolt"&gt;Judgment Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_ShadowsRetribution"&gt;Shadows Retribution&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_Annihilation"&gt;Annihilation&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_RayOfTheInfernalPhoenix"&gt;Ray of the Infernal Phoenix&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_BewitchingBolt"&gt;Bewitching Bolt&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7eea92a7ga087g4367gaf8cg17584e6e74d2" version="2">Eldertide Explosion</content>
	<content contentuid="h9388e065gab2cg4642ga57fg6f0a5cd71b74" version="2">Triggers a [2] radius explosion that deals [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h82326ad5g0eceg45c6gb128g91912733e083" version="1">Potion of Terrain Traversal</content>
	<content contentuid="hb3969dfbg64a2g43a8g85b8g78f397edeb33" version="2">Crafted from rare herbs and blessed by nature's spirits, this elixir radiates a calming aura, swirling with hues of green and brown.</content>
	<content contentuid="h352b729ag3487g46bag9835g107f8cb94fa9" version="1">Grants immunity to &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DIFFICULT_TERRAIN"&gt;Difficult Terrain&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9b7d7b56g966cg40f9ga1b1ge5e634c2a8e6" version="1">Terrain Immunity</content>
	<content contentuid="h088bf8a9gedecg4183gab64g2893dc9fed02" version="1">Affected entity has immunity to the effects of &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DIFFICULT_TERRAIN"&gt;Difficult Terrain&lt;/LSTag&gt;, allowing free movement regardless of environmental hindrances.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc7f79aa4g23b2g49e8gb82cg87d67f12f418" version="1">Elixir of Unleashed Chaos</content>
	<content contentuid="hb33c918cg449ag4fd7g9935g342d609727c2" version="2">Infused with flickering sparks of untamed energy, this elixir seems to pulse erratically, promising unpredictable yet potent effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="haf88a109gb6e7g4115g9371g21cd5355ef08" version="1">When attacked, you can use your reaction to unleash a wild magic surge upon your attacker.</content>
	<content contentuid="he9d4c6d3g5fc1g4f33g902agd922ed8033f3" version="1">Chaos Surge</content>
	<content contentuid="ha0e8364egc37eg4762g8446ge9eba69d4a11" version="1">When attacked, you can trigger a wild magic surge, releasing unpredictable magical effects against the attacker.</content>
	<content contentuid="he889d30agdf4cg4245g84a5g2988c13c75f3" version="1">Unleash Lightning</content>
	<content contentuid="h89f4e173gad03g442dga5c0gb208871ca362" version="1">Creates an eruption of electricity and lightning.</content>
	<content contentuid="h29094c49g8960g4465g9a76ge2b2fe47c515" version="1">Chaos Unleashed</content>
	<content contentuid="hceb9bae8gdcaeg403eg9548g000b37717232" version="1">When a foe hits you with a spell attack, you can use your reaction and unleash Wild Magic Surge uppon the attacker.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf34d6d3fg6a07g4c9cga95ag1b4f1b730d7b" version="1">Unleash Chaos</content>
	<content contentuid="h9271d5ddgd124g4983ga637ge3ad7eb93759" version="1">Target an enemy spellcaster. They will unleash a wild magic surge on themselves.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcff37373g0525g42faga860g7152f5931507" version="1">Elixir of Obscure Necrosis</content>
	<content contentuid="hf29e9d2cgd479g4de1gb270gc4cdf441ccf9" version="2">A shadowed essence, foreboding and potent, swirls within this vial, emits an ominous aura, shrouded in whispers of the undead.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0a4d1d70gdaf0g4077g8a5dg4701c6b00a8a" version="1">Your melee attacks deal extra [1] when attacking from obscured areas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Replaces the effects of other Eldertide elixirs upon consumption.</content>
	<content contentuid="h08e407c9g1b2cg423fgb3b5g11e1218f826a" version="1">Obscured Necrosis</content>
	<content contentuid="h6df608d2g6856g469fgaaadg883181a80f67" version="1">Provides additional [1] to melee attacks when striking from obscured areas.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb1b0d862g173cg423cg8e45g2deff0c3cb7c" version="1">Obscured Necrosis</content>
	<content contentuid="hda818edbgf839g4e47g868eg1cbf3d89421e" version="1">While in obscured areas your melee attacks deal additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hfcfa2cb1g7568g421dg9d74g2e67fe45a300" version="1">Elixir of Charismatic Brilliance</content>
	<content contentuid="hebba6561gd215g45f0gac56gf49f1b5fcd08" version="2">A blending of rare herbs with ethereal essence, this elixir shimmers with a captivating aura.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf761bbcegf24eg414cg82f9gb7c520e9cdd8" version="1">Grants proficiency in all charisma skills and a +2 bonus to charisma.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha624d9aege922g4092gb573g631109f5dc2c" version="1">Charismatic Brilliance</content>
	<content contentuid="h4a922ba6g5ba6g435cga8cag4e852081b25d" version="1">Affected entity gains proficiency in all charisma skills and a +2 bonus to charisma.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcbcc7e20gc28cg45ccga402gf970b908f4ef" version="1">Divine Restoration</content>
	<content contentuid="h7e6a300bge223g4973gbd11gf75c3490d60b" version="2">Calls upon celestial energy to heal and renew, mending wounds and restoring vitality.</content>
	<content contentuid="h30e6d03bg6e2fg41a7gb688gedcd414573d3" version="1">Divine Beam of Recovery</content>
	<content contentuid="h1c3f98adg7309g4039g8321g7656d31a65d0" version="1">A superior healing spell of immense power, allowing you to channel your healing energy into a focused beam of rejuvenation.</content>
	<content contentuid="h25c31357ge730g4a88gba65g517ca08091bd" version="1">Psychic Surge</content>
	<content contentuid="hc7d988a6g2f25g482eg99b3g9eef039161f1" version="1">Unleash a sudden and intense burst of psychic energy, damaging all nearby enemies within your radius.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1ec79a11g0c09g457bgb5efg6190dcdfcb4a" version="1">Flame of Agni</content>
	<content contentuid="h10c16bb0gc919g460dg9a71g763644b54895" version="1">Skadi's Glacial Strike</content>
	<content contentuid="h1c4247b4g99f7g465bg8bb9ge1200105d107" version="1">Ra's Sunfire Grasp</content>
	<content contentuid="h84e3d9f2g5d55g49c0g87a6g455818d4d6b5" version="1">Wrath of the Skyfather</content>
	<content contentuid="h8fb6df0fgcba5g4be1gac53gb46d70b8a23c" version="1">Tlaloc's Kinetic Tremor</content>
	<content contentuid="he09f027eg1b75g4a6dg92ebg86cec5afe810" version="1">Mercury's Mindstrike</content>
	<content contentuid="h5599a164g2512g4211g912fg0c8c67801dfb" version="1">Your unarmed attacks deal an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h700dd578g18f0g45f9g898cgaf63cf436303" version="1">Infernal Blink</content>
	<content contentuid="hebad8291gfe4bg43a6g8212gc709c43aa4af" version="1">Infernal Beckoning</content>
	<content contentuid="h87360537g7d87g400eg9436g2b158be54707" version="1">Ethereal Resurgence</content>
	<content contentuid="h76d5d8e9g87d7g4cd9g939eg88e05027deec" version="1">Restores a fellow party member to full health, an immensely potent ability that can shift the tide of the battle.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4ef00073g5d6eg43e9ga7c1ga1d622f0089b" version="1">Scorching Talons of the Firehawk</content>
	<content contentuid="h04c69dc6g7183g4959ga7d8gc4dcfff6dec5" version="4">Unleash a flurry of [2] blazing, high-powered projectiles, each dealing [1]. They always find their mark.</content>
	<content contentuid="h917e1eb1g88ccg432ag9512g9d96b0dc6c4a" version="2">Reckoning of the Dual Flame</content>
	<content contentuid="hf8c1058eg0df0g48afgaeb1g2bf38601bc66" version="2">Unleash a white pillar of radiant and necrotic fire, a fusion of holy and profane energies.</content>
	<content contentuid="h11bb97d4g81fdg4659gae95g8a3e2c1fdf84" version="1">Ray of the Infernal Phoenix</content>
	<content contentuid="h6177e673g8df4g442bg9272g5be519f43739" version="3">Channel the fierce, unending might of the infernal phoenix, unleashing a searing ray of fire. Inflicts [1] and engulfs the target in flames.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4c7f5befg064dg4d5ag8933g75480f64fa45" version="2">Hellfire Ward</content>
	<content contentuid="ha83b6365g6ff1g4266g996bge9fe3c7611a5" version="1">Infernal Defense</content>
	<content contentuid="h18da7cd9g541fg4676g9599g802d3d8124a4" version="1">Infernal Domination</content>
	<content contentuid="h2b8bf475gb735g480ag8185gc4cc0734117c" version="1">Devil's Scorching Grasp</content>
	<content contentuid="he2fbfd45g93dbg477dg88f9gb1b459191f27" version="1">Hell's Protection</content>
	<content contentuid="h297e6038ga6e2g4389gae76gdf3dfeecfe48" version="1">Conjure a Defensive barrier that makes creatures and objects inside it &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to all damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hafe707d8g95a0g419dg91begf66a4c81a756" version="1">Harness the might of the hells in battle as you beckon forth a fiendish ally.</content>
	<content contentuid="hff1590ebg22aeg49cag8608g53cf8e06c554" version="1">Hellfire Pact</content>
	<content contentuid="h580a0bc9gdcfeg4a9ag9008gf20918c5ae1d" version="2">Hellfire Pact: Drakthul</content>
	<content contentuid="h86a4accdgc1f1g4721ga9b5g1f8f72e22f45" version="1">Hellfire Pact: Ravenna</content>
	<content contentuid="hd8f2186bg13b0g40dbga44eg8249f1b5220e" version="1">Hellfire Pact: Mizora</content>
	<content contentuid="ha0173935g8535g4bafg8197ge8d8759dfd4a" version="4">Drakthul</content>
	<content contentuid="hd15a2c39gc99bg4da0g991eg39ef8327b51e" version="1">Ravenna</content>
	<content contentuid="h1bc3ff57gf4b5g4ac0g8c6ag561a2da0f463" version="1">Mizora</content>
	<content contentuid="h9401ed98ged70g4351ga83dgda4989878ab2" version="3">Form a vengeful pact and summon Drakthul, the formidable Half-Demon warrior, as your loyal companion who will wield his malevolent might to aid you in your fights.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8c7e157fg2001g4a1cg876dg227ace448cd4" version="3">Forge a dark covenant and summon Ravenna, the mighty Half-Demon Protector, as your unwavering companion who will channel her infernal powers support you in your endeavors.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3967667eg97b2g43fdg823cg1cffce8bf64b" version="3">Enter into a sinister pact and conjure Mizora, an otherworldly Half-Demon, as a steadfast companion who will harness her demonic abilities to assist you in your endeavors.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha86ba7cdg3df6g4d0bg91b3g9c591b6c1ea5" version="1">Mighty Onslaught</content>
	<content contentuid="hf32607bfg5e7ag4b68gaf42gebea3e42d097" version="1">Gains a +1d4 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2164c9edg7d47g4714g8c8egefd3448cafcc" version="1">Dark Vanish</content>
	<content contentuid="habb9214cg271ag491dgadc8g6e5c71f44b08" version="1">When you eliminate an enemy using a melee attack, shroud yourself in a veil of darkness, rendering you &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="INVISIBILITY"&gt;Invisible&lt;/LSTag&gt; for [1] turns.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfa6cdb56gaf32g4f1egb442g9958f10359e8" version="1">Cataclysm Blast</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a2db382g38b9g4091g9283gc4c2b8ce7bb6" version="3">Channel the arcane might within you to conjure [1] colossal, crimson, crackling energy beam(s), capable of unleashing a devastating surge of force that deals [2].</content>
	<content contentuid="h3655de75geee9g4b70g803eg807e8adb025a" version="1">Marked For Negation</content>
	<content contentuid="h40c18563g6a3dg4d2dgbd78gf6b5f63dad95" version="1">The target's defenses are compromised, resulting in a reduction of their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; by 2 and their &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellDifficultyClass"&gt;Spell Save DC&lt;/LSTag&gt; is lowered by 3.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd389fa24g8dadg4acdg8afegfbef223b0042" version="1">Guardians of Icewind</content>
	<content contentuid="hf44c5ba6ga0dfg481agacc2g5d097ec84e3e" version="1">Summon the fearsome beasts to stand vigil by your side in the heat of battle, reinforcing your ranks with an indomitable force.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbe49b858g78e0g4cc7ga37agbe51ff7d82a5" version="1">Summon: Aquila</content>
	<content contentuid="hbcfe56b3gf32ag4bc6g8183g4b92bcc5b158" version="1">Summon: Huginn</content>
	<content contentuid="ha848ea0dg6789g4d03gb57cgbef6d738093c" version="1">Summon: Guenhwyvar</content>
	<content contentuid="hfe977adag3930g4488gb26fg43c46dac89b6" version="1">Aquila</content>
	<content contentuid="h1f65ca05gd5aag4d5dg8cfbg98854d8185dd" version="2">Huginn</content>
	<content contentuid="hd773863bg1031g4aa4ga4dage65fceb0d89b" version="1">Guenhwyvar</content>
	<content contentuid="hf711357eg5c6cg43cagb3acg40d926665327" version="1">Drizzt Do'Urden's legendary feline companion.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7961c6afg6a47g4a8egaf63gbcc655f0202c" version="1">Summon Guenhwyvar, the Ethereal Feline Companion to aid you in your adventures.</content>
	<content contentuid="h64909649g65abg4809ga8e1g36911e65670c" version="1">Piercing Scratch</content>
	<content contentuid="hec9c3edcgbb17g40e4g9dbbg3fcb1e6033a1" version="1">Scratch a target with a powerful attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbfcca039gb19cg49efg9bb2gc14f75c4ffd1" version="3">Drizzt's Legacy</content>
	<content contentuid="h728a3383gfe20g4042gb152g39713db0cafe" version="5">Embrace the legacy of Drizzt, gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; with scimitars, daggers and longbows.</content>
	<content contentuid="h70c5896egaacbg40a8g8193g53371f240c13" version="1">Death Step</content>
	<content contentuid="h771a51b5g36f1g4ceegbd1cg2dad4f4cbfce" version="1">Riftbreaker</content>
	<content contentuid="h4b0df642gadf6g48e1g8276g36aeed997d26" version="1">Hell's Blessing</content>
	<content contentuid="h0fff165dg84e4g4934gba74g58c53abf9f67" version="1">You gain a +[1] bonus to Spell Attack Rolls and Spell Save DC.</content>
	<content contentuid="h53964b4ag3119g4c78g83c8gdddf8e255534" version="1">Celestial Warding</content>
	<content contentuid="h26fa81d1geadcg42eag9b59g060549cdc605" version="1">Grants you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Radiant damage and empowers your weapon attacks with an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hb49f1e93gd7ecg42d7ga2c5g8afc6be31231" version="1">Shapeshift</content>
	<content contentuid="h92cda727g3b96g4973ga508g1a890f52e55e" version="1">Tap into your ancestral animal heritage by entering a primal trance that lets you transform into various creatures, gaining their unique abilities and enhancing your adaptability</content>
	<content contentuid="h13d6105bg431fg4776gbc51gcd48e7b7741e" version="1">Morphic Recovery</content>
	<content contentuid="h1d514b22g4fa7g44b5g8c84g807f1e158c85" version="1">As your bond with shifting forms intensifies, you gain the ability to rapidly heal and rejuvenate, bolstering your resilience in the heat of battle.</content>
	<content contentuid="he3aa2537gf4f0g4509ga9f8gba5667c0e2dd" version="1">Lesser Morphic Recovery</content>
	<content contentuid="hae036fceg0156g477bg953dg918823467434" version="1">Tap into your shapeshifting affinity to mend minor wounds, demonstrating your growing control over form and healing.</content>
	<content contentuid="he277a478g81e6g4affgba9dgab1251279299" version="1">Advanced Morphic Recovery</content>
	<content contentuid="h061db992g4b6cg4cd9gb0e1g11ad31ea6fab" version="1">Unleash your shapeshifting prowess to heal injuries more effectively, showcasing your mastery over the connection between form and healing.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1ac67840ge9b0g4ea8ga41ag81baf679be36" version="1">Health must be below 70 percent.</content>
	<content contentuid="h80d8de70g5774g458cgbcc1geed8b6ee044c" version="1">Greater Morphic Recovery</content>
	<content contentuid="h7632ca9agf8b9g45f4g9b56gad485234110a" version="1">Channel your profound mastery of shapeshifting to mend severe wounds, showcasing your unparalleled control over the symbiotic relationship between form and healing.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3cdb1342g81f6g44d5g87f2g18ab2f865714" version="1">Health must be below 50 percent.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdff836ccgb908g41aeg9c85gc0a54ef18268" version="1">Verdant Armory</content>
	<content contentuid="h08fa2b42g4decg4ea2g8a8bg6acdd8f38e5c" version="1">Grants &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; with Martial Weapons, Light Armor and Medium Armor.</content>
	<content contentuid="h44bf6f3ag4ca5g447eg8573g4ae9c71e3059" version="1">Feral Swiftness</content>
	<content contentuid="h13fd45edg98a4g4a1cg9331geebe0ce51689" version="3">Awaken your primal instincts and unleash your inner beast to Gain &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FERAL_SWIFTNESS"&gt;Feral Swiftness&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef32d985g60bdg4369gbce7g8134f758910c" version="2">Affected entity has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Dexterity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;, its &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; and jump distance is doubled, and it can take one additional action per turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf9ed4b21g98cag4691ga775gf0495d7f1b7c" version="1">Shapeshift: Cat</content>
	<content contentuid="hfaf9c630g1491g414ag91f2g45c1c75b3b81" version="3">Shapeshift: Sabre-Toothed Tiger</content>
	<content contentuid="ha4b20434g8c8ag406fg889ag119d0d2fc290" version="2">Shapeshift: Owlbear</content>
	<content contentuid="h11d3d777gaad3g408cg88eage4e3cbdcdcf3" version="1">Shapeshift: Black Bear</content>
	<content contentuid="h2acd1771g96abg48cegac02g2db8168120d9" version="1">Assume the shape of a Black bear that can Goad enemies into attacking it.</content>
	<content contentuid="h400d07ccg20f0g4fadgb947g963ba31e8402" version="2">Skyward Soar</content>
	<content contentuid="h042654b8g071eg4157ga387g45925bb9ac3e" version="2">Infernal Wings</content>
	<content contentuid="h3c3f1b1eg6ff6g4b6dga3f0g51e48b6b4605" version="1">Absolute's Call</content>
	<content contentuid="h5bf14386gf60dg41e6gad92gbf50d9f0ce38" version="1">Channel the unwavering devotion of the Absolute cult, bringing forth loyal followers who stand ready to serve their dark and mysterious cause.</content>
	<content contentuid="h184d38bcg053eg43c2ga129g3c7ee345e975" version="1">Dror Ragzlin</content>
	<content contentuid="h79674a3bgf26fg4c0cg8118ge185bf8a20f0" version="1">True Soul Nere</content>
	<content contentuid="hcbba9311g145cg4833g9271g42becac5d4a4" version="1">Minthara</content>
	<content contentuid="hfbd913cag21c5g4261ga639g810a5c01d619" version="1">Flaming Fist Marcus</content>
	<content contentuid="h2e44bbf8gedd2g4993g87d6ga861d431f818" version="2">Absolute's Call: Dror Ragzlin</content>
	<content contentuid="h6977b61cg05e0g44c9gb040gf06c66d2f7d3" version="2">Absolute's Call: True Soul Nere</content>
	<content contentuid="hda83c0bdg4997g4bd4g8b47gf7e08659c033" version="2">Absolute's Call: Minthara</content>
	<content contentuid="h98b28520g21d5g4087gbf3bgab292ccc53eb" version="2">Absolute's Call: Marcus</content>
	<content contentuid="h1092ee49gf60eg4224gb877g00b186726222" version="3">Summon Dror Ragzlin, the fearsome hobgoblin barbarian whose unwavering loyalty to the cult is equaled only by his relentless and untamed might.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2386ea0fg2a53g4d0eg87ebg649bcf9a289e" version="3">Summon True Soul Nere, the formidable sorcerer of the Absolute cult, whose mastery of arcane forces is surpassed only by his unwavering dedication to the cult's cause.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbf5e1e81gf9b7g49d0gafe4g81f58391b202" version="3">Summon Minthara, the devout servant of Lolth and resolute commander within the Absolute cult, whose unwavering faith in her dual oaths bolsters her allies and strikes fear into her enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="h004fe968g15c7g4008ga2fegeec23b28c462" version="3">Summon Marcus, the darkly devoted paladin in the service of the Absolute, whose necrotic power and unwavering allegiance strengthen your cause and sow dread among your foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a3719c9g1bc7g451ega0dcg186b766cf383" version="1">Absolute's Warden</content>
	<content contentuid="hd6ddbfb5gc209g4efcg942eg9f77fba2f927" version="1">Grants &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; with Martial Weapons, Light Armor, Medium Armor and Heavy Armor.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5194f3bag3d53g4fdaga1b4gb74a54ee7201" version="1">Malediction of Ruin</content>
	<content contentuid="h22e26778g299cg45fdgb9beg75fa2adb7dec" version="1">Ruin's Victim</content>
	<content contentuid="ha012b95bgc829g4312ga948g532ee7ca5f58" version="1">Has a 1d4 penalty to Attack Rolls and Saving Throws.</content>
	<content contentuid="h294b23f1gf47fg4635g8a99g8bef5daa9e8b" version="1">Aard</content>
	<content contentuid="hcad1aafcgf7dfg4c23g9c1egeb3c53ede5eb" version="1">Igni</content>
	<content contentuid="hc439aa1dg8e82g4b61gb4c3g68e6f178bdac" version="1">Quen</content>
	<content contentuid="h7e9417a0g5082g4707g91bcge67a35ad92de" version="1">Yrden</content>
	<content contentuid="h222924bbge7e6g40a2gaeaagfe5fbd475ce7" version="1">Axii</content>
	<content contentuid="h2149fe2age1d6g4358ga4cfg40ad6327c846" version="1">Harness the force of Aard to release a powerful gust of wind from your hand dealing [1], knocking back and potentially making foes in front of you &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb71b0634gf708g4293gab96g67d1ab616c0c" version="1">Channel the power of Igni to unleash devastating flames from your hand. engulfing your target or area in searing flames, dealing [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h53b8d048g3a4fg40f4g86b9g5b147f9ef6b0" version="1">Invoke the protective magic of Quen to create a shimmering force shield around yourself. Grants you 20 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;Temporary Hit Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Slashing, Piercing and Bludgeoning. While Quen is active, those who strike you will endure [1]. </content>
	<content contentuid="h689bffb9gb02fg42cega13bg2430772adbad" version="1">Create a magic seal on the ground. When a creature enters the seal, they take [1] and [2]. The targets must succeed on a Wisdom &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; or become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PARALYZED"&gt;Paralysed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h882dd7efg2e00g41c3gae98gcf78f382c9c1" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Only one yrden seal can be active at a time.</content>
	<content contentuid="h443a9b9cgb450g4cc4g8946gabdbfa3f6524" version="1">Utilize the mesmerizing power of Axii to temporarily &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CHARMED"&gt;Charm&lt;/LSTag&gt; an enemy, causing them to become friendly and fight by your side.</content>
	<content contentuid="h48849aebgef79g4a24ga2a6g992d0c238444" version="1">Granting 20 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;Temporary Hit Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Slashing, Piercing, and Bludgeoning damage. Those who dare to attack you while the shield is active will suffer [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h062baebdg1703g4ae1gb5afga4f6ea22b892" version="1">Quen Ward</content>
	<content contentuid="hd8fd725egb20fg4d90gb5a3g02e8ad32b666" version="1">Yrden's Sealing</content>
	<content contentuid="h3056fe72g0181g4a64g993dg97f9a96a87af" version="1">Axii's Enchanting</content>
	<content contentuid="hd3e36202g9f75g46b6g8917g38482b848eba" version="2">Witcher Signs</content>
	<content contentuid="h38f40f40gfd48g464cg92efgc96c08608340" version="3">Yrden</content>
	<content contentuid="h7da2cc1cg3894g4ee1ga75bga3af814d83df" version="2">The Witcher's signs are at your disposal, ready to be wielded at will.</content>
	<content contentuid="h970178bdgc7bcg41d9g9644g00adda6508f4" version="2">Trial's Fortitude</content>
	<content contentuid="hdbb25633gf3e7g47f9g848agcceda4a368ab" version="2">Your body, fortified through the Trial of the Grasses, grants you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Poison damage. You gain +4 bonus to initiative rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdab3e197g2edbg43dcgb2ecg16bbb993e506" version="1">Hunter's Sense</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f556494g0cc3g4f74gaaa4g1910eaaa73ed" version="2">Witcher's path is unforgiving. Your journey as a monster hunter has taught you to excel against the supernatural. You have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; against Undead, Fiends, Beasts, and Monstrosities.</content>
	<content contentuid="h414dc04ag2575g4fbbg8b26g12a2bd4a04eb" version="1">The Great Hunt</content>
	<content contentuid="h3e431246geb32g40ceg9a73g8b5a909800d5" version="1">Gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; when targeting Undead, Fiends, Beasts, and Monstrosities.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b4b85dag3e0fg40daga2abga1b227e7ba6a" version="2">Bladecaster</content>
	<content contentuid="h8b835c68g1fb0g4fd3ga831g186e94080c55" version="3">Channel your signs into your weapon, forging it into a conduit of untamed elemental forces. Your strikes manifest as surges of arcane power, dealing 1d4 damage of your chosen type.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7c75ed7bg614dg43f3ga25fg44fe47b5e430" version="2">Igni's Blaze</content>
	<content contentuid="h739ac121ge71bg4101gb244g584b5f297af8" version="1">Channel the power of Igni into your weapon, causing it to burst into flames. Your melee attacks deals an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h94bff763g2d70g4499ga1e0gbc7b7fb5df03" version="2">Aard's Shockwave</content>
	<content contentuid="h29729a97gae72g4fafgb506g63158b90b0b8" version="2">Infuse your weapon with the power of Aard, crackling with thunderous energy. Your melee attacks deals an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hf82b9d66g1340g4768gb17agca43a5f316df" version="2">Quen's Resilience</content>
	<content contentuid="he86ee688g53a0g4fc4gaf66g7e8fb93a4662" version="3">Channel the protective aura of Quen into your weapon, creating a shimmering force. Your melee attacks deals an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hc3d0a27bgbd0dg4cd8g9b94g5b2690d53e96" version="2">Yrden's Radiance</content>
	<content contentuid="hbe1b0911gb2f6g415agbbe6g00bf8e69f262" version="2">Enchant your weapon with the radiant energy of Yrden, glowing with purple light. Your melee attacks deals an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h72d553efg4bdag43c4g9939gc5a7c7f34b84" version="2">Axii's Enchantment</content>
	<content contentuid="h321c0086g0fc0g4780g9cceg20c320e5002f" version="2">Imbue your weapon with the psychic influence of Axii, creating an otherworldly aura. Your melee attacks deals an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h9c16c354ga06cg451eg89d5ge0407f9ed1d3" version="1">Sign-Channeled Weapon</content>
	<content contentuid="h59a9da80g893cg4f3egb472g1689187d9bf3" version="3">Your weapon has been infused with energy, attacks with this weapon deal extra damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h368d34f2g7dedg4afcg9408g3cc0e1af21c0" version="1">Judgment Bolt</content>
	<content contentuid="hc0acd6c2g1848g4121ga509g1ccc12f7f21e" version="4">With a fervent prayer and a raised hand, you call upon the divine wrath, channeling the righteous fury of the gods into a powerful bolt of divine energy. A powerful single-target bolt capable of dealing an immense [1] to enemies or heal ally for [2].</content>
	<content contentuid="h12945acag782cg4442gb4e5gfcc44d749466" version="3">The target of Judgment Bolt is branded with the Divine Verdict, which carries one of two effects based on their alignment. &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PURIFICATION"&gt;Purification&lt;/LSTag&gt; radiates healing energy, mending the wounds of allies, while  &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CONDEMNATION"&gt;Condemnation&lt;/LSTag&gt; inflicts radiant damage upon foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0d77733dg7ec9g4b2eg8da7g4ec4e1a59883" version="2">Divine Verdict: Purification</content>
	<content contentuid="h5305d782ge124g4202gac34g8b1d4064d437" version="3">Throughout the next 3 rounds, the affected target regains [1] at the start of each round.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7491ace4ge394g4fdcg8b40ga391668700af" version="2">Divine Verdict: Condemnation</content>
	<content contentuid="h3eab94bfgfafbg4ab1g9cf5g7a3dbb2e43fe" version="3">Throughout the next 3 rounds, the affected target takes [1] at the start of each round and has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and you gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on attack rolls against the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1593f8eegb218g4301gb245g69b02e56f785" version="1">Shadow's Retribution</content>
	<content contentuid="h85cbda5dg9e26g43dfg9985g8974054a4e45" version="4">Summon the wrath of Shar to conjure [1] mighty beam/s of shadow-infused energy. The beam/s pierce through the battlefield, delivering a devastating [2] to the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="h916b9e84g91a6g4d4cg9f66g55b8ca7bd53a" version="3">If the enemy fails its saving throw against the spell, it becomes &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLINDNESS"&gt;Blind&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcc6bfc17g777cg4c79gb89cg32a5094204f7" version="1">Dragonkin Heritage</content>
	<content contentuid="h5fb3ba12g703bg4fb2g89f9gc7d40f9657a0" version="1">Drawing upon your Dragonkin Heritage, unleash a potent breath weapon that embodies the elemental essence of your draconic ancestry. Flames, frost, acid, or lightning surge forth, bearing the indomitable mark of your dragon bloodline.</content>
	<content contentuid="h81b85b16g949bg4814ga117g3083ca82f575" version="2">Drakarion's Inferno</content>
	<content contentuid="h57a5a65cgb2c8g4d05g8a04gcf7642b59dd0" version="1">Unleash a searing inferno upon your foes, engulfing them in scorching flames. Dealing [1] and subjecting them to &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="INFERNO_GRASP"&gt;Inferno's Grasp&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h00bb5be4g5b85g4152g9890gc9c8a80393a8" version="2">Aurorion's Chill</content>
	<content contentuid="h46679817g83a5g4ba9ga788gddf8541d69b6" version="1">Unleash a frigid blast upon your foes, encasing them in freezing ice. Dealing [1] and leaving them &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ICESHIVER"&gt;Iceshivered&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2775fc57gefccg4a7bga7c1g4dffb36aef04" version="2">Nyxara's Corrosion</content>
	<content contentuid="h3071ac84gecb0g4f9fga63age331ef3cfbe6" version="1">Unleash a torrent of corrosive acid upon your foes. Dealing [1] and leaving their armor &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CORRODED_ARMOR"&gt;Corroded&lt;/LSTag&gt; and weakened.</content>
	<content contentuid="h75c4379ag1bb7g4f22g95a8g4a366ff49891" version="2">Celestriax's Lightning</content>
	<content contentuid="h14d91f53gd43fg491cga175g25173c698031" version="1">Unleash a surge of electrifying energy upon your foes. Dealing [1] and leaving them &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ELECTRIFY"&gt;Electrified&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha0807d4ag7ebbg4250gb86eg233dadc4d0f3" version="2">Inferno's Grasp</content>
	<content contentuid="h24cc63d7g025cg4217gb5e6gcdd8f3c89e09" version="1">Dealing [1] at the end of the turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9d0938b8g1c79g45edg907cg492a94f07a40" version="2">Iceshiver</content>
	<content contentuid="hcf14fb25gb0b9g494cg8072gcc113945e871" version="1">&lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; is halved, dealing [1] at the end of the turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6cc81d8cgecc1g423bgbadag69e4cf5a7ca1" version="2">Corroded Armor</content>
	<content contentuid="h42c56549gab4eg4289ga725gc5aa515260da" version="1">Armour Class has been reduced by 1.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd06a5b90g4a06g40edg8c4agc96f4280215b" version="2">Electrify</content>
	<content contentuid="hb0e111d1g1184g47c5g833eg00d6523ed133" version="1">Unable to take &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Action"&gt;action&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="ReactionActionPoint"&gt;reaction&lt;/LSTag&gt;, attackers have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcfb7712dgbc4bg4c29gae6fg0caa3131629d" version="1">Dragonplate</content>
	<content contentuid="h0e8f9eabg0fb9g45a4ga622g8ec32e1f151e" version="2">Grants 10 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage</content>
	<content contentuid="h91162e50g4f9cg42d5ga9e1ga57b6654515b" version="1">Draconic Retaliation</content>
	<content contentuid="h5ad9df10gf8e8g4fe0ga33eg7c60804a9b21" version="1">Upon entering combat, your draconic blood surges, granting 10 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Physical damage for 1 turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc01b6288g6957g4abaga80dgfa21b8ebc2a4" version="2">Frost Tempest</content>
	<content contentuid="hc4de0d97g127eg425cgaab7ge6006c9fa430" version="2">Evoke a chilling tempest of ice and frost to descend from the sky, blanketing the earth and striking all objects and creatures within its range.</content>
	<content contentuid="h41637d96g519bg4a1dg9549g19f1b4993db1" version="1">Cryomancer's Mark</content>
	<content contentuid="h919597e8g3fb0g4240g863bg8b61c45580aa" version="5">Invoke the icy arts of the cryomancer and brand a target with a shimmering sigil of frost. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, they suffer &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FROSTBITE"&gt;Frostbite&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6670e341g47dbg4ecega9e2g0c83812be200" version="1">Frostbite</content>
	<content contentuid="h416918b4ga0b4g4defg9658gd54e77e2d8d9" version="6">The target's movement speed is halved as the icy chill of the mark hinders their mobility. The target becomes &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Vulnerable"&gt;Vulnerable&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Cold damage, and have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disdvantage"&gt;Disdvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5081128ag8a53g469cgb819g7c7c5638ec8d" version="1">Soul Drain</content>
	<content contentuid="hdb7c6db5g51feg4f68gbd71g41e4083b19b7" version="3">Upon striking your foe, you siphon their life force, dealing [1] and healing yourself for the amount of damage inflicted.</content>
	<content contentuid="h02fdfdadg9813g4a49gaf83g06a3d6960aa8" version="1">When cast on a Humanoid or a Beast, they will be affected by Soulbind.</content>
	<content contentuid="h70f99479gcf6fg4fd6gbc15g7adfba59689a" version="1">Damage Done</content>
	<content contentuid="h39571711g04e5g4825ga3a3g6b032752d5d6" version="2">Soulbind</content>
	<content contentuid="h87ec2fafg8bb9g4c74ga8ddgbb5038f936f1" version="3">The affected entity is weakened, experiencing a halved movement speed and a -2 penalty to damage rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2adee310g0d21g467eg8e0bg6401d388c3f7" version="2">Annihilation</content>
	<content contentuid="h89a76577g1d0eg4591g8c9agc3700952272e" version="5">Unleash a sinister, emerald ray from your outstretched hand. If the [1] reduces the target to 0 hit points, they crumble into a pile of ashen remnants.</content>
	<content contentuid="h14f121c7gc368g4db7gb82cgd0574bf75b63" version="1">Revenant's Fury</content>
	<content contentuid="hea756434gfb47g457bgb22bg26f0402f019e" version="1">Unleash the wrath of the vengeful revenant, draining the life force of those nearby and becoming the harbinger of death. As it deals [1] in a radius, you also gain &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DEATHS_RESONANCE"&gt;Death's Resonance&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="UNDYING_EDGE"&gt;Undying Edge&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef3552aegd3a4g4c54gad83g7811fe9fced0" version="1">Death's Resonance</content>
	<content contentuid="h57cf5b29ga430g416dg899cgf3088b1369b1" version="1">You gain a +2 bonus to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and become &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Immune"&gt;Immune&lt;/LSTag&gt; to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="CriticalHit"&gt;Critical Hits&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h121aba2bgdf5fg4f45g8c39gf1d928c01a1c" version="1">Undying Edge</content>
	<content contentuid="hcf1b50ceg1c5dg40ffg9032gcda3dbff03d3" version="1">Upon activating Revenant's Fury, you draw power from the abyss, infusing your weapon with unholy energy. Your melee weapon attacks now deals additional Necrotic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7df74d25g14ccg4ffeg9111gc2ed1a31dac2" version="2">Trickster's Sanctuary</content>
	<content contentuid="h4b5d75ccgc630g461fg8efagc6be65621156" version="6">Conjures an ever-changing dome, filled with mischievous energy. Upon entering, allies receive &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ETHEREAL_VIGOR"&gt;Ethereal Vigor&lt;/LSTag&gt;, boosting their defenses and attacks. Enemies, however, fall victim to the &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="ETHEREAL_ENSNAREMENT"&gt;Ethereal Ensnarement&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd02158ddg6e21g4ed9ga5ccgc625a9b1863d" version="2">Trickster's Sanctuary Aura</content>
	<content contentuid="h726f4457g42cdg4c48g8d76g606e37c65804" version="6">Within the Trickster's Sanctuary, allies granted protection while enemies face the Trickster Might.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha933b4c5gd1e4g45f9gabdbg39ad3a1fe2ce" version="2">Ethereal Ensnarement</content>
	<content contentuid="hee49a23fg4c57g4c63ga3eegd7ccb8f531ce" version="6">Take [1] at the start of each turn while inside Trickster's Sanctuary. Have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; is halved.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfb0c0868g56a8g4477g9bcegbb505bc37fc8" version="2">Ethereal Vigor</content>
	<content contentuid="h67759397g1981g4fe8gb934ga51620e07f42" version="6">Grants a +2 bonus to  &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armor Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; and your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; are made with &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You can't be &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt; inside the dome.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4b778ab0g89fag472agae57ga9541c8fce3e" version="1">Fool's Luck</content>
	<content contentuid="hb029fb74g7ebdg4f26gbb6cg42e5bc6a1585" version="2">You possess an uncanny knack for avoiding danger and tricking your foes. You Gain immunity to surprise and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; psychic damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha70854b0ge89dg40c4gabe7gce83f5c69968" version="2">Bleeding Edge</content>
	<content contentuid="h87259758gdfc5g481bgb215g83c1169c50ac" version="2">Your every strike carries the potential to draw blood, Possibly inflict &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;Bleeding&lt;/LSTag&gt; when you attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcdd2c978gaa12g4f40g83d9gf114453e73d3" version="2">Mindwarden</content>
	<content contentuid="h74349980g1961g41c9gb13fg7d54e6c0a64d" version="5">When you succeed on a Saving Throw, the foe responsible takes [1], and you gain +[2] bonus to Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma Saving Throws.</content>
	<content contentuid="he3e8ad76g9c2fg4a7ega694geae2b178dde6" version="1">Astral Surge</content>
	<content contentuid="hebb25666g7b46g41edgbd6agbc01795d36b2" version="1">When you land a killing blow on an enemy, you gain a temporary surge of vitality that heals you for [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h9b7d1dadga210g4a09g933bgcca7198836d4" version="1">%%% Tech Status Astral Surge Heal VFX</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb8e2ab7ge02cg45c5ga0ddg9a898a0b517e" version="1">%%% Tech Status Astral Surge Heal VFX</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1449a18g19dfg445fgb63bg1d372b072461" version="1">Astral Arena</content>
	<content contentuid="hcd399066g73f4g4325g8f1dg73ab2b31118d" version="4">Conjure a shimmering ring around you. Inside this mystical battleground, your allies gain Psychic &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt;, are shielded from being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CHARMED"&gt;Charmed&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and weapons deal additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h08a6dd6ag425cg4871ga7a3g402875d27d94" version="1">Astral Commander</content>
	<content contentuid="h7212fea7gd9aeg4708g8acbg21d9c5daf124" version="2">Nearby allies gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Psychic damage, immunity from being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CHARMED"&gt;Charmed&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt; and weapon attacks deal an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hd99ef44cgb2feg4b72g89bag543f8ef25bf5" version="1">Astral Soldier</content>
	<content contentuid="ha014baf1g06ffg4959gb9ebgbaf5099fa154" version="2">Gained Psychic &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt;, immunity from being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CHARMED"&gt;Charmed&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Frightened&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Attacks deal an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h3ae19c4cga6b5g4966gbd68gce14934987e0" version="1">Astral Arena Effect</content>
	<content contentuid="h5d6afb66gde49g4576g9b79g493bd9611a99" version="2">Mindflayer's Bane</content>
	<content contentuid="heb2fe459gc6f5g4648ga599gab6c8326344e" version="4">You utter a guttural, Githyanki incantation, focusing your energy on a single target. If the target has [1] hit points or fewer, it dies instantly. If it has more than [1] hit points, it takes 55-100 Damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf681c335g634cg4dc4gbceeg4df23fa5a3f6" version="2">Ethereal Alliance</content>
	<content contentuid="h21c6b782g38ceg4ea4ga0e7g3dfb0eab3cd5" version="2">Thalos Drakorin</content>
	<content contentuid="h38eb734fg789eg44efga4b9g33bca18e2d37" version="5">Kythra Vrathal</content>
	<content contentuid="h9bc4932bgd1c0g4480gbaa2g50cc2524ab61" version="3">Draw upon your profound connection to the Astral Plane, summoning forth fierce and devoted Githyanki warriors to stand by your side.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf4d86cd6gede1g4287g9cf7g2f5d630f1ed1" version="2">Ethereal Alliance: Prince Orpheus</content>
	<content contentuid="h04260184g5e40g495bgaf4fg4f1e24270cc9" version="3">Channeling your psionic energy, you invoke the presence of Orpheus, the Githyanki Prince. A true guardian of the Astral Plane, to guide you in your path.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb0e0a514ga108g48b7ga5f6gb9670eeea336" version="2">Ethereal Alliance: Thalos</content>
	<content contentuid="h72a9b228ge3a6g494eg9e8fge83f817ea736" version="3">Drawing upon the eldritch might within you, you beckon Thalos, the formidable Githyanki Warlock, to stand with you in battle. A master of otherworldly invocations and eldritch knowledge.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc90bdf10gd887g47fbg8c18g85dd4a950e0c" version="2">Ethereal Alliance: Kythra</content>
	<content contentuid="h90366a40g4160g4302gb633g507c248d481d" version="3">With a focused invocation, you call upon Kythra, the formidable Githyanki Eldritch Knight, to join your side in the heat of battle. A master of martial combat and arcane magic.</content>
	<content contentuid="h57aa7e8egc371g4139gb472gd57527d7459e" version="2">Thor's Fury</content>
	<content contentuid="h13bb9b97g24beg4b8bg94c4g9d121fa16b6e" version="18">Harness the mighty powers of the God of Thunder! You enter a &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="THOR_FURY"&gt;Stormbringer&lt;/LSTag&gt; state. Gaining access to &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Target_Lightning_Punch"&gt;Lightning Punch&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Shout_EirsBlessing"&gt;Eir's Blessing&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_MightyDive"&gt;Mighty Dive&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Rush_AsgardianCharge"&gt;Asgardian Charge&lt;/LSTag&gt; abilities.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc2215b47gaffeg4b59g829ag62b4d4b50787" version="3">Gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Physical, Lightning and Thunder damage. You have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;saves&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h68906780g89feg47aeg827dga23683d107a9" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Thor's Fury ends early if you don't attack an enemy or take damage each turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbf310b82g6affg4b7egb87dg7d4387abff43" version="2">End Thor's Fury</content>
	<content contentuid="hc6f372e0g384dg426agb3e1g1c6dacdaa7f8" version="3">Use a bonus action to end Thor's Fury.</content>
	<content contentuid="h01a64269g668dg41d9ga122gcd3d85261830" version="2">Stormbringer</content>
	<content contentuid="h6f34cbe8gb84eg452cgbf1ega6a8a117b999" version="1">Deals an additional [1] with melee and improvised weapons, and when throwing objects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Physical, Lightning and Thunder damage. Has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannot concentrate on spells.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb252d7adgf913g418cg9601g692aa247d3ee" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Stormbringer ends early if you have not attacked an enemy or taken damage during your last turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb81dcab8g1fbfg4e50g9208ga873d7df9ed3" version="1">Lightning Punch</content>
	<content contentuid="h5e488dbeg397bg4ba9g8722gdeefab93a700" version="3">The affected target loses the ability to react, suffers &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and endures [1] at the start of each turn. Additionally, attacks against foes wearing metal armor are made with &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h498aacbcg40cbg42d8gaf03g743c4d3e89d4" version="1">Lightning Punch</content>
	<content contentuid="hcd682e32gf0fdg46aeg8237g37dcab254790" version="1">Cannot take reactions and suffers [1] at the start of their turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1bcbedb5geb1ag4ff1gb34bgf9f208de0518" version="2">Might of The Skies</content>
	<content contentuid="ha1d976a1gdf2ag496bga775g46c4a9053ddc" version="3">Channel the fury of the storm and unleash its wrath upon all targets within range. Deals [1] and [2], you can select up to [3] area of effects.</content>
	<content contentuid="h856ba482gd6deg4d3bgaeffg7f8d86a56a7a" version="3">Eir's Blessing</content>
	<content contentuid="h17fc48e1g144ag41e9g8fd8ge90225567370" version="6">Draw upon the divine favor of Eir as it mends your wounds and heals you.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9caf6948g055dg4a3bg900eg9711c6b4dbb7" version="2">Mighty Dive</content>
	<content contentuid="h84c42cdag6679g4a3egb61cg53dd661a76fd" version="12">Leap down unto a foe, knocking them &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;. You won't take falling damage. You must be above your target.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7d6e97c8g8f6eg4993gafffg5d609955321f" version="2">Asgardian Charge</content>
	<content contentuid="h071f9aeegafa0g4a68g8f93g1c7910b7a4af" version="4">Charge forward with thunderous speed and unbridled force, attacking all enemies in the way and possibly knocking them &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="PRONE"&gt;Prone&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hda0d1899g1e6fg42ddg8c49g45772b23b6f2" version="1">Thor's Fury</content>
	<content contentuid="hebd487acg33afg44c0gb83eg340d2afad113" version="2">The God of Thunder makes you stronger. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to Physical, Lightning and Thunder damage. You gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h18d47c1bg8391g4c86gb6f7gba7d19a21656" version="2">Odinson's Legacy</content>
	<content contentuid="h00ad4110g05c2g4670ga040gfc83664b069d" version="5">While in &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="THOR_FURY"&gt;Stormbringer&lt;/LSTag&gt; state, you can use &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Target_Lightning_Punch"&gt;Lightning Punch&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Shout_EirsBlessing"&gt;Eir's Blessing&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Projectile_MightyDive"&gt;Mighty Dive&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Rush_AsgardianCharge"&gt;Asgardian Charge&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcbdd1c00g5c78g427agb806g72b427c23110" version="2">Unyielding Tempest</content>
	<content contentuid="hf4860c57gedc7g4523gba67gbd00ab2af346" version="4">The wearer gains &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;melee attack rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; while surrounded by [1] or more foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd3c537b3g1141g4e40ga2eag2ce308d30161" version="2">Stormlord Mantle</content>
	<content contentuid="he4aa2c59g4cb7g462bgacc6ge268d6768c37" version="3">You gain Proficiency and Expertise in Persuasion and Intimidation.</content>
	<content contentuid="h263ce09cg3484g4b64gb815gd5b9b7b27bb3" version="1">Skybreaker Smite</content>
	<content contentuid="hbf236da2g0208g41b5g9dc1g858a18fa7bda" version="2">Unleash a mighty lightning strike with your weapon. The impact pushes the target [1] and may knock it prone.</content>
	<content contentuid="h72f19a23g62e9g43a4g8b6dg7d55106b5cd6" version="1">Executioner Movement</content>
	<content contentuid="h828cba95g0ac0g4f92g8c8ag7d4f10b5e2c7" version="1">After vanquishing a foe, your movement speed is instantly restored to its maximum.</content>
	<content contentuid="h246cf1c5gdc3ag43a8g885ag007f5577eb7b" version="2">Logarius's Final Embrace</content>
	<content contentuid="h4e09dc21gcb8ag4e48gada2g44fb45003df5" version="4">With the ancient and unholy knowledge at your command, you utter a blood curse incantation that invokes Logarius's dark legacy, delivering [1] to a single target. There is no escape.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd289e28fg1a94g448fgb93dg9a324ab5865e" version="2">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; You take half the damage dealt.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfe8a25a6g9449g4459gada7gcc0de89ca2c9" version="2">Lifesteal</content>
	<content contentuid="ha8a79b17gf403g409bg8a1cgaa0f882c19ca" version="1">Unleash the darkness within, dealing [1]. On successful hit the target start &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;Bleeding&lt;/LSTag&gt;, suffering ongoing damage. Your life essence surges as you gain &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLOODFLOW"&gt;Bloodflow&lt;/LSTag&gt; for 3 turns.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf6592158g62efg4ec0gbbe5g50cb658343af" version="2">Bloodflow</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a27f5aeg19a9g430agb02dg4be9a9c84c3d" version="3">With the power of Lifesteal coursing through you, regain [1] at the start of each turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h68ab8cddg7894g4ff5g8f35gb6eeebe5f194" version="2">Bloodborne</content>
	<content contentuid="h3c0b5d0bg22e6g4f8agaaf3g6b55f125691a" version="2">Channeling the surging power of darkness, you willingly sacrifice a fourth of your life essence, trading it for heightened strength. As you embrace this sacrifice, you enter Bloodborne state, shrouding yourself in a crimson aura of energy that both fortifies and empowers your very being.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9ea8b986g70a5g4c2egbf9cg9904993ca9f2" version="2">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; You sacrifice fourth of your health.</content>
	<content contentuid="haf55da06g3c1fg42aeg880dg944e370d4a47" version="2">Bloodborne</content>
	<content contentuid="ha695d776gff0cg49bag81c0gc31413d802e8" version="3">You gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to necrotic damage. &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="FRIGHTENED"&gt;Fear&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLEEDING"&gt;Bleeding&lt;/LSTag&gt; effects hold no sway over you. Your melee weapon is imbued with a powerful &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="BLOODBORNE_CURSE"&gt;Curse&lt;/LSTag&gt; that can inflict necrotic bleeding on your foes, and its &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="Passive_Tainted_Strike"&gt;Tainted Strikes&lt;/LSTag&gt; allows you to deal additional damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h65ae56d2ge4e6g4aedgacaegf94a22477694" version="2">Tainted Strike</content>
	<content contentuid="hde60770bg4d6dg4365g817bge8640be21b58" version="2">Melee weapon attacks deal an additional [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="hdfe5e57ageacag4bd8g8985g7e7a54e37774" version="2">Bloodborne Curse</content>
	<content contentuid="h10e47d81gf7fbg498fg9302gcd6d2ae1065c" version="1">Inflict [1] upon your target, target must make wisdom saving throws or suffer Necrotic Damage overtime.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4b501716g0571g4e50g8653g0f36138e2ed7" version="1">Bloodborne Curse</content>
	<content contentuid="hc69d6b3ege14fg47afg8f02g315fe69ca48d" version="2">Affected entity takes [1] at round start and have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Constitution Saving throws. Can be removed by healing.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4566a191gd821g459agbe6dgf222e5dbbb82" version="1">Bloodsworn Knight</content>
	<content contentuid="h08fd6965gacecg4ac4g89f9g05343953dcee" version="1">Cursed Awakening</content>
	<content contentuid="hb0cc9383gb875g464cgbca0gc0d919e738c3" version="1">Call upon the Bloodsworn Knight from the remains of a fallen foe, ready to serve and defend you. It's a dark and unholy resurrection, turning the fallen into a loyal guardian.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9027b76fg4e49g4328g87e3gc91ba006c2f6" version="1">Predator's Precision</content>
	<content contentuid="h9fed6f48g6466g4bb7g89cfg1577fcbf76f7" version="5">You become more accurate when attacking creatures already injured, gaining a +[1] bonus to your Attack Rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="hed0b2d71g02ddg4445g8f0cg5e13b526d3bd" version="1">Stormbringer's Aftershock</content>
	<content contentuid="hd993be90geca5g488dg9f66gc3af0c0a447c" version="5">When you trigger &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Shout_Thor_Fury"&gt;Thor Fury&lt;/LSTag&gt;, hostile creatures within a [1] radius must succeed in a Wisdom Saving Throw, or they suffer [2] damage. Targets receive half the damage on a successful save.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0df13decga55dg470egb140g8b9dc2c50829" version="2">Selûne's Grace</content>
	<content contentuid="hc55f4028g4183g4c42g9e2cg3d9183b91d0c" version="3">Blessed by the divine favor of Selûne, at the start of each turn, you regain [1] hit points.</content>
	<content contentuid="h417c7922g6ce2g4a9dg8083g03eb8c2a3d53" version="1">%%% Start Round Heal Technical</content>
	<content contentuid="h9e0b4746gc98bg41abg8cf1g9e47ce9e4674" version="2">Midas Touch</content>
	<content contentuid="h2bedf685g0f11g41cbgbd5bg518e81f46491" version="3">Immobilize a target, and after 3 rounds, the target transforms into solid gold, remaining in this state until the spell's duration expires.</content>
	<content contentuid="h326018bcg48f3g46bcgbd59g8c84a469c2b1" version="2">The target will become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="MIDAS_GILDED"&gt;Gilded&lt;/LSTag&gt; if it does not succeed on its &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; within [1] turns.</content>
	<content contentuid="h298ccc80g16d6g4ed9g9b1egd0ff3f517702" version="1">Midas Touch: Stage 1</content>
	<content contentuid="h455486bfgdf7eg42a7g8047gd3c8848d9cec" version="1">Midas Touch: Stage 2</content>
	<content contentuid="he57d3ec0gf38ag4451ga3afge73fb915ec9d" version="1">Midas Touch: Stage 3</content>
	<content contentuid="hec1c1a12gecbag4390ga2c6g4ef19e241b05" version="1">Gilded</content>
	<content contentuid="hdd74df5ag5015g4ca0gb522g60b0e35c30f1" version="1">Turned into solid gold. Incapacitated and unable to move or take actions, bonus actions, or reactions.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd34870aeg7535g4b31g8d74gcb9977c3a37e" version="2">Wish</content>
	<content contentuid="hf146a1dbgba45g478fg9ec3g456f0344ca2c" version="2">Wield the might of creation and make a wish to restore an expended resource of your choosing or to grant upon you certain benefits.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc704399bg85d3g4146g881dgef72a6c6bee4" version="2">Spell Slots Restoration</content>
	<content contentuid="h050a8d2fg0722g48a1g8214g35928634d951" version="4">Recover all expended spell slots.</content>
	<content contentuid="h35b40f97g5cf0g47afga947g68a3fc7007dc" version="2">Resources Restoration</content>
	<content contentuid="hfb5a09c4gdffdg45c7g8f19g25c7a5f7689e" version="4">Recover your expended class resources.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8ba95fafg96deg49e4g9d71g7d9948c10b26" version="2">Dispel Curse</content>
	<content contentuid="haca70e6dg803eg4f0dgb643g1e9be5237abd" version="4">Eliminate any current curses and hexes that have taken hold of you.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8b7282cdg0d2bg4f00g8c4dg416035695004" version="2">Chest of Provisions</content>
	<content contentuid="h379feef7g6f53g443aga34cg090a0299ecb7" version="3">Summon a chest filled with essential camp supplies, healing potions and elixirs.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd45a498ag5ba9g4df7gb58fg7b15834987e7" version="1">Available only outside of combat.</content>
	<content contentuid="h146440c7g5001g433ag8eb0g6cd836211301" version="2">Mental Maelstrom</content>
	<content contentuid="h8b4aeebeg1a83g4d51g9064g052e5a8cfcab" version="3">Breach into an enemy's mind and tear it down to pieces, dealing [1]. Inflict &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Attack Rolls and Dexterity Saving Throws, you gain Attack &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="hac004ab5g60eag4196ga1d8g62f28fa218b6" version="2">Mental Maelstrom</content>
	<content contentuid="h0e9ad86age268g47degb541g03b9fcaed88b" version="5">Has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Attack Rolls, Dexterity Saving Throws and becomes easier to hit.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2908a5e8g4710g47f5ga191g6e865c74d515" version="2">Hill Giant Form</content>
	<content contentuid="h53e0f65ag11dag4c50ga5d4g9b7442e96f89" version="3">Grow to a gigantic size. Your weapons deal an additional [1] damage and you gain [2] and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8e028049gab91g4b18gb499g7e2409ca3a40" version="1">You gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Ability Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt; using Strength, and weapon attacks deal an additional damage.</content>
	<content contentuid="hde876e0fg138dg40e7g9869gcb871911cc5c" version="2">Hill Giant Form</content>
	<content contentuid="hf41dcf71gd5ebg4abag9a0dg23db42c48ce9" version="4">Affected entity's size is increased. Weapon attacks deal an additional [1] damage. It gains [2], and has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Strength &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb558c4e7g2dacg436ag92bcg3a4150b62d6b" version="2">Hill Giant Endurance</content>
	<content contentuid="h5f94f0bagb9a6g43afgada1g510db6bca529" version="3">Gained [1] &lt;LSTag Tooltip="TemporaryHitPoints"&gt;temporary hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8c7f0321gb7d3g4dd4gb8d2ge7c4e2f805b7" version="1">Hoarfrost Counter</content>
	<content contentuid="hd26ee961gf8cbg4981g95b7g1210c3fec9f2" version="2">A shield of cold vengeance protects you. When struck by a melee attack, your icy aura inflicts [1] upon the attacker.</content>
	<content contentuid="h04e9667dg10f3g4fabga642gdf247b08d855" version="1">Hoarfrost Counter</content>
	<content contentuid="hd4771205g8981g4b0dga8c1g5098ac82fbf8" version="1">Unwavering Spirit</content>
	<content contentuid="h6429de63g66afg4268gbf88g2dea904cc0b1" version="1">You are immune to the Frightened condition and cannot be subject to other emotional influences.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd79c0eb8g04a7g45e8g80e1g013d4a3c2a55" version="1">Wrath of Avernus</content>
	<content contentuid="h77c70551g24f7g4104gac7agaadb51243c69" version="1">You are the Wrath of Avernus, a feared force, both by demons and devils alike. Unleash a fiery burst that deals [2] to all around you within a [1] radius. You gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to fire damage and +1 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;, with each successful attack you accumulate a stack of &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="WRATH_OF_AVERNUS_COUNTER_0"&gt;Avernus's Wrath&lt;/LSTag&gt;, building toward a &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="WRATH_OF_AVERNUS_ACTIVE"&gt;searing assault&lt;/LSTag&gt; upon your enemies.</content>
	<content contentuid="h25cf9b5egdeadg4eebg9a96g2407f1092cd2" version="1">When the condition ends, you're left &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="WRATH_OF_AVERNUS_EXHAUSTED"&gt;Drained&lt;/LSTag&gt;, for harnessing such fiery might takes considerable effort, and everything has its price.</content>
	<content contentuid="he03573d8ga756g4d25g9f39gbd8212f289f9" version="1">&lt;LSTag Type="Image" Info="SoftWarning"/&gt; Will drain character power when condition ends.</content>
	<content contentuid="h58485d92gfd20g4203gb1e1g69b66cc7b22a" version="1">Avernus's Wrath</content>
	<content contentuid="hd031a87fg4d4eg45ddg8101g3b9366e18ae4" version="1">Avernus's Wrath: 1</content>
	<content contentuid="h104a5e16g7ac1g4842gac8cgefedb5441654" version="1">Avernus's Wrath: 2</content>
	<content contentuid="h7aea72d1g526ag45cag9501g130392724dd1" version="1">Avernus's Wrath: 3</content>
	<content contentuid="h55ad320cgda70g48ebg9b7bg990adf9aa7db" version="1">Your legacy hasn't been forgotten! After four attacks, you can unleash the devastating &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Target_AvernusSearingSmite"&gt;Avernus Searing Smite&lt;/LSTag&gt; upon your enemy.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0ab7e854gf072g4abdg8222g6165478d4e4c" version="1">Wrath of Avernus</content>
	<content contentuid="h3caf8051g8e76g4789gad13gaa83e5fd348d" version="1">You are the Wrath of Avernus! for 3 turns you can unleash the formidable &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Target_AvernusSearingSmite"&gt;Avernus Searing Smite&lt;/LSTag&gt;. After activating &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="ELDER_Target_AvernusSearingSmite"&gt;Avernus Searing Smite&lt;/LSTag&gt; you become &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="WRATH_OF_AVERNUS_EXHAUSTED"&gt;Drained of Power&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="h67fb737egd8b8g4c8cg9d65g8507148b195d" version="1">Avernus Searing Smite</content>
	<content contentuid="h5ac8361cg3a76g4f94gadc2g99e2b1187b83" version="1">Your weapon attack deals an extra [1] and sets the target on fire, causing them to suffer an additional [2] every turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7a466f01g0968g4b6dga57dg7e5d17d8e868" version="1">%%% WrathOfAvernus Technical Status</content>
	<content contentuid="h657630acg8909g4d54g9b93g1bbd34cbcf84" version="1">Drained of Power</content>
	<content contentuid="h6d550a71gcb7eg4bfcg9c4eg3e7ce8bdcd60" version="1">The entity is drained of its power, its movement speed is halved, and it has 1d4 penalty to attack rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd35afd93gc309g4958g8cf4g5c170557c2fa" version="1">Bewitching Bolt</content>
	<content contentuid="h40dcbc86g1facg4375gb12bg7f13eda9f3f6" version="3">Unleash a deadly enchantment that combines the power of lightning and mind manipulation into a single mesmerizing beam. On impact, it deals [1] and [2] while &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="CHARMED"&gt;charming&lt;/LSTag&gt; the target.</content>
	<content contentuid="h205fb9a6g2195g4ca1g8d57g34d57b644603" version="1">Dreadful Backlash</content>
	<content contentuid="h9a89fa24g7acdg442cg8069g8471f0368760" version="3">Counter your foe with a burst of psychic might that deals [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h5bf7d9cfg521bg4452g8bcfgec0e0da274aa" version="1">Dreadful Backlash</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd66b076ge7c1g492bg8762g6103ce3b9060" version="1">Counter your foe with a burst of psychic might that deals [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b8bcd59g88cbg41bdg81f1g16fa6e301f56" version="1">Dreadful Backlash</content>
	<content contentuid="h3ba517c2gc301g46d6gb46fgcef6a11eee79" version="1">When a foe hits you, you can use your reaction and counter with a burst of psychic might that deals [1].</content>
	<content contentuid="h265cca1cg1b90g403dg8198gd80a1287d4b0" version="2">Witch Queen's Cauldron</content>
	<content contentuid="h36840ff4g9af3g4729gafd7g27caa6af4d62" version="3">Summon forth the enchanted cauldron of the renowned Witch Queen Tasha, brimming with mystery and the alchemical potential to craft potent elixirs and potions.</content>
</contentList>